in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create a color palette from
如何从创建调色板
the colors in a pixel-based image using
使用基于像素的图像中的颜色
inkscape so the first thing you'll want
所以你要做的第一件事就是
to do is import your image onto the
要做的是将图像导入到
canvas as I've done here with my example
画布，就像我在这里用我的例子做的那样
image and to sample the colors from this
图像，并从该图像中采样颜色
image we're going to use the trace bit
图中我们将使用跟踪位
map tool so I'm going to click on the
地图工具，所以我要点击
image to select it and I'll go to path
图像以选择它，然后我将转到路径
and I will select Trace
然后我将选择跟踪
bitmap now the settings I want to go
位图现在的设置我想去
with over here on the right hand side of
在这里的右手边
the screen I want to choose the
我要选择的屏幕
multicolor tab and then I want to come
五颜六色的标签然后我想来
over here to this dropdown and choose
在这里到这个下拉列表，然后选择
colors now right here where you see the
颜色现在就在这里，你可以看到
number of scans this represents the
扫描次数，这表示
number of colors that will be sampled
将采样的颜色数
from your image and you could see a
从你的图像中你可以看到一个
preview of some of those colors over
预览其中的一些颜色
here in this preview menu now if you
在此预览菜单中，如果您
notice I have eight which is the default
请注意，我有8个，这是默认设置
which you can see it includes a lot of
你可以看到它包含了很多
the colors there but it misses the
那里的颜色，但它错过了
pinkish reddish color of the Hat here so
这顶帽子的粉红色，所以
for my example I'm going to increase
在我的示例中，我将增加
this number until I get more of those
这个数字，直到我得到更多这样的
colors that I want to include
我想包括的颜色
and once you're finished all you have to
一旦你完成了所有你要做的
do is click the apply button and give it
所做的就是点击Apply(应用)按钮并给出
a second to process if you're using a
如果您正在使用
lot of colors like I am in my example
很多颜色就像我在我的例子中一样
it's going to take a minute or two to
这需要一两分钟的时间来
process okay so the trace is finished
处理正常，因此跟踪已完成
I'm going to click and drag the trace to
我要单击并将轨迹拖动到
move it away from the
把它从
image and then I'm going to select the
图像，然后我将选择
image and press delete on the keyboard
图像并按键盘上的Delete键
to get rid of that cuz we don't need
为了摆脱那些我们不需要的东西
that anymore I just want the vector
现在我只想要向量
colors here and I'm going to ungroup
颜色在这里，我要解开分组
this so I will go to object and I will
所以我会去反对，我会
select
选择
ungroup and once you've done that you
解组，一旦你这样做了，你就
can click off of the image to deselect
可以在图像上单击以取消选择
everything and you could zoom in to all
所有的一切，你可以放大所有
of the vector-based elements here to see
在这里查看基于矢量的元素的
the different colors that you could
不同的颜色，你可以
sample so I'm going to start off with
样本，所以我将从
this pink shade right here I'm going to
这个粉色色调，就在这里，我要
click on that to select it and if you
单击该选项以选择它，如果您
notice over here you'll see the color
注意，在这里你会看到颜色
highlight in this little stripe down
在这条小条纹中突出显示
here in the bottom left of the screen
在屏幕的左下角
I'm just going to double click on this
我只需双击这个
stripe and it's going to open up the
Stripe，它将打开
fill and stroke menu and with this
填充和描边菜单，并使用此
object still selected I want to go to
仍处于选中状态的对象我要转到
the fil Tab and then over here I want to
FILL选项卡，然后在这里我想
I want to choose this button right here
我想在这里选这个按钮
that says Swatch I'm going to click on
上面写着斯沃琪，我要点击
that and it's going to add that color to
它会把这种颜色添加到
a new Swatch and now we can go to our
一块新的斯沃琪，现在我们可以去我们的
swatches menu by going
通过转到色板菜单
to view and selecting
要查看和选择
swatches now you should see your Swatch
色板现在你应该看到你的色板了
appearing in this list here if you see
出现在此列表中，如果您看到
other colors populating here just click
此处填充的其他颜色只需单击
on this menu and choose Auto from this
在此菜单上并从该菜单中选择自动
dropdown so now that we know how to do
下拉菜单，这样我们现在就知道如何做了
that we can go add some more colors to
我们可以去添加更多的颜色
our Swatch here so I'm going to come
我们的斯沃琪在这里，所以我要来
back over here to the fill and stroke
回到这里来填土和划水
menu I'm going to choose a shade of blue
菜单我要选一种蓝色的
and I'm going to add that to my swatch
我要把它加到我的样本中
as well and if you notice each new
同样，如果你注意到每个新的
Swatch you add will be indexed in this
您添加的样本将在此索引中
menu right here so I'm going to add some
菜单就在这里，所以我要加一些
more and once you're finished once
更多，一旦你完成了一次
you're happy with all of your swatches
你对你所有的样品都很满意
you can zoom out you can press control a
您可以缩小您可以按Ctrl a
on your keyboard or command a if you're
在您的键盘或命令a，如果您是
using Mac to select everything and then
使用Mac选择所有内容，然后
just press delete because we don't need
只需按Delete键，因为我们不需要
it anymore now now we have our swatches
现在它不再存在了，现在我们有了自己的样本
in place and if you want to change the
并且如果您想要更改
color menu down here at the bottom of
颜色菜单在下面的底部
the screen just click on this menu icon
屏幕只需点击该菜单图标
over here down at the bottom right and
在这里右下角，然后
instead of inkscape default we want to
与Inkscape默认设置不同，我们希望
choose Auto and once we have Auto
选择Auto，一旦我们有了Auto
selected our chosen colors that we
选择我们选择的颜色，我们
created from the image will appear in
从图像创建的内容将显示在
the menu there and if you want to make
那里的菜单，如果你想做的话
those icons bigger you can come back
那些更大的图标，你可以回来
over here to the menu and choose
在这里进入菜单，然后选择
configure and you could CH take the tile
配置后，您就可以使用该磁贴
size and increase it like that and now
像这样调整大小并增加它，现在
you have much bigger swatches to work
你有更大的样本要工作
with down there in the bottom left
下面在左下角
corner
拐角
and now when you create new objects let
现在，当您创建新对象时
me show you as an example you can color
我给你展示一个你可以涂上颜色的例子
you your new objects using these
您可以使用这些工具创建新对象
swatches down
色板向下
here so now let's go over how you can
现在让我们来看看你是如何
save these swatches in case you want to
保存这些样本，以备您需要时使用
use them in other documents in the
在其他文档中使用它们
future now there is no way to directly
未来现在没有办法直接
save these swatches but there is a
保存这些样本，但有一个
workaround using templates so what you
使用模板的变通方法，因此您
want to do is save this entire document
我要做的是保存整个文档
as a template and then it'll be saved
作为模板，然后将其保存
with these swatches so that next time
用这些样本，这样下一次
you open a new document from that
您可以从中打开一个新文档
template you will have these in place so
模板您将这些都准备好了，这样
I'm going to come up here to where it
我要到这里来，在那里
says file and go
说归档并离开
to save
为了节省
template and I'm going to give this a
模板和我要给它一个
name I'm just going to name this
名字我只想给这个命名
nature
自然界
pallet and I'll click
托盘和我将点击
save and now if I go to file and I
保存，现在如果我转到文件，并且我
select new from
选择新的来源
template I can choose the custom tab I'm
模板我可以选择自定义选项卡我是
going to select nature pallet and click
选择自然托盘并点击
create from template
从模板创建
and in my new document I can go to view
在我的新文档中，我可以查看
select swatches and there my color
选择色板，然后选择我的颜色
palette is so that's how you can
调色板是这样的，所以你可以
generate color palettes from images
从图像生成调色板
using inkscape if you found this lesson
如果您发现这一课，请使用Inkscape
useful then consider checking out my
有用的，那么可以考虑查看我的
inkscape master class it's a collection
Inkscape大师类，它是一个集合
of over 60 videos where I go over all of
60多个视频中，我浏览了所有
the tools and features in inkscape and I
Inkscape和I中的工具和功能
explain what they are and demonstrate
解释它们是什么并演示它们
how they work kind of like how I did in
它们的工作原理有点像我在
this video we even have a private
这个视频我们甚至有一个私人的
Community where you can ask questions
您可以提出问题的社区
and get help from me anytime you want
只要你愿意，随时向我寻求帮助
and best of all there's no monthly
最棒的是没有月刊
membership fees you just pay $17 one
会费你只需付17美元一张
time and you're in for Life I'll have
时间和你在一起的生活我将拥有
some information about that down below
下面是关于这一点的一些信息
if you want to check that out as always
如果您想一如既往地检查一下
thanks for
谢谢你
[Music]
[音乐]
watching
看